大家好啊！最近如何？
Hi. How are you doin'?
我还好吧......
I'm doin' fine!
我头发大概四个月没绞了，但是这没啥。
My hair has not been cut in like four months, but that's okay.
确实没啥:-|
It's okay.
是呀，自从上回我淘二手（注：在年初）以来，事情有点太多
Yeah, some things have happened since the last Thrifts episode, you know.
啊，时间就这样慢慢地流逝了
Some time has passed. Yeah, it's just how it is.
现在的世界过于凶险奇怪
The world is a strange existence at the moment
但是这也意味这我们将有这个奇怪的一集
but that also means that we're gonna have kind of a strange episode here,
至少是这几个月淘二手录像的的集合
or at least in terms of how the footage came together
因为我好久都没出去淘了
because I haven't really been able to record anything for a while.
以往我两周淘一次
And I usually go thrifting like twice a week
然后我现在有......有段时间才淘了两次
and now I've gone I think twice in the past, oh gosh, I don't know how long.
无论如何，我把从去年十二月到今年三月间的录像都攒在一起
Anyway, I've gotten a bunch of footage together
from before that, from like December to March,
那就是这个视频了
and so that's gonna be in this video.
还有，我把好多以前没用过的老剪辑放在这里收尾
Also, I've just ended up using a lot of old footage
that was not in previous episodes.
反正放这也没啥目的
It was just cut for whatever reason, you know.
我也没想故意凑时间
I didn't want to fit it in there for time constraints
也不是因为足够有趣才放这里
or I didn't think it was interesting enough.
无论如何，这就是了！
Whatever, it's in here now!
当然最近的录像也有
And then a little bit of recent footage too
因为那里一个月前重开了
because things did open back up a month or so ago,
然而现在又关门了，所以就很......
and now they're closing back down again so I don't know.
记得看着的东西还是有 很多的吧
It has a mishmash of all kinds of footage so,
无论如何，咱们走吧！咱们淘二手去！
whatever, just roll with it. Let's go thrifting!
LGR淘二手第四十五集：特殊时期特辑
LGR - Thrifts Ep.45 Unprecedented Times
啊，今天天气真好！
Alrighty, it is a good day for a Goodwill
所以让我们走进GoodWill然后看看有啥好货吧！
so let's head inside and hope what we find is will-y good!
呃，走进店里我看见了一堆单曲和专辑黑胶
And directly up near the front is a buggy of B-Sides, and A-Sides, and LPs,
还有各类唱片
and vinyl records of all different types.
十二寸的，七寸的，四十五转的
12 inch, 7 inch, 45s,
底下是成堆的十寸虫胶
and down below that were these stacks of 10-inch shellac records
看起来大概是来自上世纪三四十年代
actually from late 1930s, early '40s, it looks like?
平常看不见这些古董像这样堆在一起的
Don't usually see so many of them stacked together like this.
呵呵，八成是有人把他们家所有的收藏都给扔了
And yeah, I mean, somebody was just getting rid of their whole record collection, it looks like.
只是都给处理了:-(
Just cleared them all out.
这还有一箱箱盒子上写来自Angie's Closet 的唱片
There were boxes and boxes of records from "Angie's Closet," according to the box writing.
然后走到这还有一个黑胶唱机
And then over near that was a record player.
也就是Soundesign牌的吧
It is one of these little Soundesign things
我时常遇到
I run across every so often.
木头装饰得好看，但除此之外也就没啥了
Got some nice wood, but nothing terribly special,
就是那种塑料做的自动化唱机
just kind of a plasticky automatic thing.
我也不喜欢看见这个16转挡
I do like seeing any with the 16 RPM on there.
也就拿这个超慢速放唱片还有点用处
It's just fun to play certain records really slow.
我们俗话叫Chipmunks（原意是美国常见的一种松鼠，此指变速播放）
Chipmunks, anyone?
走到那里我看见了一篮子好东西
Over near that was another basket of goodies.
一堆磁带
Bunch of cassette tapes,
还有这堆VTech V.Smile（注：这玩意相当于咱们的步步高平板）的配件
as well as a selection of these VTech V.Smile thingies.
在这也是不很常见
Don't normally see that many in one spot,
还有这些Scrabble Flash迷你游戏机
or for that matter, these Scrabble Flash games.
之前也没见过
Never seen those before.
Ohh，看看这个
Oh, look at this.
你绝对能想到这个曾经是
You could tell this used to be
一件完美的充满木纹（LGR的最爱）的艺术品，但是呢
a beautiful wood grain piece here but, yeah,
这玩意太破旧了
it's been rather gutted.
这是台老式收音机
This is an old radio,
也许应该修复一下
perhaps a restoration project at some point.
原来这是Philco牌的，型号38-7
Turns out this is a Philco Model 38-7,
显然“38”代表着上市的年份
the "38" apparently indicating the year that it was introduced to the market,
至少Philco Radio Gallery（Philco Radio 图片在线展览）是这么说的
at least according to the Philco Radio Gallery.
上面写着当年要卖80美金呢
Apparently it originally sold for $80 back in the day
而且这还是这个的姐妹型号呢
and this was one of their console versions of it,
这个还配备了”不用蹲下，不用弯腰，不用斜视“的特色控制面板
offering the No Squat, No Stoop, No Squint inclined control panel.
曾经倒是个大件
Used to be a gorgeous thing.
我确信有人会来翻新的
I'm sure somebody could restore it
只要你有足够精力和钱的话......:-(
if you had the, you know, restoration wherewithal.
那后面有两个电子琴
Over behind that had a couple of digital pianos back here.
上面那个不是下面那个包装的型号
This one on top is not the one for the box.
上面的是个雅马哈的YTP-240
It's a YTP-240 by Yamaha on top here
而盒子里的是NP-11，看上去挺吸引人的
and inside the box was an NP-11, which I quite prefer the look to.
只是看上去更加简洁一些
Just much simpler,
与前面形成鲜明对比的是这个......The Hamzer的？
In stark contrast to whatever this is ... The Hamzer?
是这么念吧
I don't know.
看起来也就三十五块钱（五美元）成本的便宜货
Looks like it maybe cost about five bucks to manufacture.
手感不是很好
It did not feel good.
然后嘿，来看看这个老影音中心
And hey, look at this AV center.
上面是上拉开的玻璃门
It's got this nice hinged glassed area up here,
中间放老显像管电视
place for a CRT in the middle,
然后呢，下面就是些媒体介质
and, yeah, like media storage down below.
唤起了我奇怪的逝去年华
Brings back weird nostalgic memories.
看见了这个Royal牌打字机
Got a Royal typewriter over here,
古旧的，吸引人的设计
a rather appealing old design,
尽管我不知道这玩意型号是啥，而且也不知道到底值不值得翻新
although I don't know exactly what model it is or, you know, if this would even be worth restoring,
不过这设计倒是让我赏心悦目
but I just kinda like the way that these look.
瞧那些又大又笨重的大按键
Just the big ol' chunky bits in the middle.
然后我看见这些耐人的七八十年代电子产品
And then we've got this lovely assortment of late '70s, early '80s.
看看，这大个混音台
Look at all this. Got a big ol' powered mixer over here,
这俩Radioshack的大音箱
a couple of speakers from RadioShack,
和这豪气的 Zenith System 3 大电视
and a gorgeous looking Zenith System 3 TV over here,
他们Space Command（太空司令）系列产品之一
one of their Space Command ones.
天啊，这真是太耐人了！
Aw man, this thing looked amazing.
可惜只有RF信号输入
A shame it was only RF.
要不是这样，我也许就拿下了
I probably would have gotten it otherwise.
看上去是85年生产的
I think it was manufactured in '85
后面铭牌是这么写的吧
is what it said in the back?
84年？呃，我忘了......
'84? I don't remember.
但是呢，电视是真耐人
But, yeah, just a lovely looking TV.
这俩音箱也是
These speakers, too.
十分吸引人，这实际上是MC-1000s
Quite appealing, as well as an realistic MC-1000s,
为Radioshack制造，由Radioshack制造......不管了
manufactured for RadioShack, by RadioShack, whatever.
反正是Radioshack卖的
RadioShack sold them.
然后再来看看这Peavey牌XR-1200接电混音台
And then there's this, the Peavey XR-1200 powered mixing console,
个人以为是79，80年生产的
I think manufactured around 1979, 1980.
绝对是一台怪兽级别的机器
Just an absolute monster of a machine.
看上去真不错
Wonderful to look at.
他们卖875块钱（125美元)
They were selling it for $125.
也不知道这玩意现在哪里还用得到
I don't know what use it would be really to anyone at the moment,
但是无论如何，这设计令人起敬
but, man, the construction of this was just admirable.
再看看这些输入输出接口，还有其他的，XDR啥的，我的妈妈咪啊！
And check out all of the inputs, outputs and everything, XLR, oh my goodness.
真是台挺大的老机器了
Just a beautifully overwhelming bit of old hardware.
尽管如此，我又回去耐了耐这台老电视
Still though, I kept going back to that TV.
我一直都很喜欢这些Space Command系列的产品
I've always liked the Space Command things.
我曾经搞过两台，但不是这台
I've got a couple myself but not this one in particular.
我希望有人能把它买回家然后耐不释手
I hope whoever bought it ended up having some fun with it.
说到好玩，看看这里的玻璃箱子
Speaking of fun, check out the glass case over here.
你不会在GoodWill经常看见这些
You do not see these too often at Goodwill.
这是台Tandy TRS-80彩色电脑
This is a Tandy TRS-80 Color Computer 2
随附一个磁带机用来加载数据
with the tape deck for loading stuff
然后他们要价1400块（200美元）
and they were charging $200 for it.
这就难以接受了
That's a little stupid.
尽管如此，在这看见老货还是很高兴
Still though, nice to see any kind of CoCo at Goodwill.
这个我只能猜测与那边架子上的电脑相关
And I can only assume this was related over on another shelf in the other side of the store
这是台TRS-80 DMP-120点阵矩阵打印机
We had a TRS-80 DMP-120 dot matrix printer.
245元（35美元），价格更加公道
$35, much more reasonable.
而且还附带一箱纸
And it came with a box of paper
还有一点办公用品和其他
and a little mount for your desk and everything, yeah.
土有点多，但整体上品相很好
Dusty, but overall actually pretty good condition.
还有电缆和诸如这类的东西
It's got the cables and such.
被买走只是时间问题
An admittedly tempting prospect.
好啊B-）
Hello there!
这就是一堆拼图和桌面游戏了
And checking out the puzzles and board games,
只是来看看有没有感兴趣的放在这里
just to see if anything is stuck in here
因为我好久没来了而且他们就这么摆在这里
since I hadn't visited in a while and it's all, you know, somewhat organized today.
然而并没有，这并没有我感兴趣的，诸如盒装电脑游戏之类的
But no, there's pretty much nothing in terms of, like, stuff I'd be interested in, big box PC games.
至于搜遍全店所找到的盒装软件
About the only big box software I saw in the whole store here
只是这个Microsoft Works Suite 99（Office精简版）
was this random little copy of Microsoft Works Suite 99.
你懂的，没啥特别的
You know, nothing terribly interesting
但毕竟是盒装软件
but it is a big box software release
里面还有料，卖14元（两美元）......好吧:-|
with some things in it for two dollars. Ehh, y'know.
在电子区内，这个Harman Kardon扬声器更加吸引我
Much more exciting to me were these Harman Kardon speakers over in the electronicals section.
不过说实在的，这东西没那么有趣
And, I mean, they're not really that exciting,
不过这设计倒很滑稽
but they got kind of a funky little design going on.
还有这米白色外壳，我喜欢
And beige/off-white computer speakers, I approve.
我还喜欢这个
And I also approve of this,
这个BSR频谱分析与均衡器，型号EQ-3000
the BSR Frequency Equalizer Spectrum Analyzer Model EQ-3000.
而且还是图形的呢
Yeah, it's a graphic equalizer.
不得不说，的确很吸引人
A rather attractive one, I gotta say.
294块嘛（42美元）......要不是家里已经有的话，我就买了
$42. If I didn't already have a pretty similar one, I would have grabbed this.
上面呢，我们看见了一个十分吸引人的老VCR录像机
Up above here, we've got a rather appealing-looking old VHS camcorder,
一个Magnavox EasyCam
a Magnavox EasyCam.
这里的小滑门十分吸引我
What attracted me to it was this little sliding bit here.
看看，可耐人了
Check this out, I like this.
而且这里啥功能都有呢:-)
Look, it's got all these features on here.
淡出呀，背光呀，聚焦呀，自动计时器呀
Fade, backlight, focus, self-timer.
那这角度独特的塑料破烂又是个嘛呢？
What is this angular-lookin' plastic thingy?
啊，居然是时钟+收音机+灯光三合一
Yeah, we got a clock radio light contraption.
不知为何，我看这玩意又爱又恨，这挺好
I don't know why but I, this kind of thing, it appeals to me, it grosses me out, I like it.
反总觉得这玩意有点内涵
I don't know, there's something cool about this.
就这么粗犷地放在一起，但结果还不差
It's like so cheaply put together, but yet it's got its own identity.
确实耐人
It's lovely.
这个就有点意思了
And this was something
我一开始不知道这是啥
I wasn't quite sure what it was at first.
看上去是个老标签机或是啥的
It looked like a glorified label maker or something.
我看它就像是那么用的
I mean that kind of is what it is in the way it works,
然而，实际上这是台MAX LETREX线号机，型号LM-500
but, turns out this is a MAX LETREX lettering machine, LM-500 model.
显然它把你输进去的东西打印出来
Obviously it prints out things that you type in,
但我不知它能打印出来啥
but I wasn't sure what it printed out on
也不知这到底是干啥的
or what they were for
在我做了一点微小的搜索后
and after doing a little bit of research,
我才明白这实际上是将字符字母之类的
it turns out that this was actually for making text and characters and things
打印在一个透明橡胶条
that print out on transparent ribbon
然后你可以剪下来然后可以贴在
that you can cut out and put on to,
诸如商业幻灯片用的投影片等等
like overhead transparencies for business presentations and such.
其他吸引我的是
The other really cool thing that grabbed my eye
这机器里面还有字体卡附件
was the fact that it had these font cards that go in on the side,
这个小卡带，加入了更多的字符
these little cartridge slots, adding even more letters.
毕竟，这是台线号机，它就是干这个的
I mean, it's a lettering machine, that's what it does.
Wow，看看这个木纹装饰的多合一机器
Aw man, look at this woodgrain-clad all-in-one mixture device kind of thing.
一个Fortronics的电话、收音机、闹表
A Fortronics telephone, radio, alarm clock.
我的天，这玩意可真全能而且这还有免手提功能
Aw man, it does so much and it even has hands-free mode.
emmmmmmm，有点意思
Heh-ho! Fancy.
还有这个米黄色和木纹，你无法拒绝的
And that beige and wood grain combo, you can't beat it.
来这里瞧瞧这堆老旧家电
Man, there was quite the string of older electronics here this time.
说真的，看看这个
Seriously, look at this.
Sylvania便携式唱片机
Sylvania portable record player.
型号是Exponent 4/40 solid state
It's an Exponent 4/40 solid state.
这有低音，高音。响度，和声道平衡调节
Bass, treble, and loudness, and balance knobs.
只是要价1575块（225美元）
Charging $225 for it though.
这还有些电脑扬声器
Got some more 90s-looking computer speakers here.
一些索尼大法产物
Some little Sonys.
这不太常见
Don't see these too often.
看上去应该是那些VAIO电脑的配件
Looks like it probably would have gone to one of their VAIO machines.
或者应该与其相关，也许不是
And maybe related to that, maybe not,
这还一个索尼VAIO键盘
got a Sony VAIO keyboard over here.
或者比这更晚上市
Maybe a little later?
我也不太清楚，一个时期的？
I don't know, same era?
这个地方倒有XP的图标
It's got an XP logo Windows key right there.
不是个太好的键盘，但是捏
Not a great keyboard, but, yeah.
索尼大法好:-P
Sony, that's a thing.
另一个老电器就在其上面
Another bit of old electronics just above that.
这个Concertmate，我只是因为这中间
This Concertmate, mostly was just attracted to it
的平衡条才被吸引来的
because of that balance slider in the middle there.
可惜的是，这后面的六个一号电池仓已经被腐蚀了
Unfortunately, it suffered some corrosion from those six D-Cells it would have taken around back,
但是设计不错
but kind of a neat design.
这里还有一个JVC牌CX-710US彩电+立体声收音机+录音机三合一
Also really neat is this JVC, the CX-710US color TV stereo radio cassette recorder.
居然就把这仨就这么放在一起
All the things in just one unit.
兄弟，我就喜欢这种多合一的稀奇货
Dude, I love this kind of all-in-one silliness.
虽然这玩意的三个组件单独拿出来没有那么好
You know, I'm sure these components on their own probably are no good individually
但他们只是把他们放在了一个银质的外壳中
but you combine them all into one silvery-looking unit
然后就成了很吸引人的老电器
and the retro appeal is kind of off the charts.
我确实喜欢这种多合一的老家电
I love seeing these kind of all-in-one things.
看看，谁想接个Zoom来的电话？
Oh, hey, anybody need to hop on a Zoom call?
这有个Zoom牌猫（调制解调器）
We've got a Zoom dial-up modem here,
型号是V.34
a V.34 dial-up Zoom modem.
还有收发传真功能
Fax-ready and everything.
我看见这大个老电气
I see a tan technology classic over here,
IBM牌打字机，型号Selectric II
it is a IBM typewriter, the Selectric II.
里面还有墨带，估计已经干了
Still got some ribbon in there, probably dried out,
但看看这大个滚轮
but check out the ball.
你可以用它打出Courier字体呢
You've got a Courier typeface ready to go.
绝对是个大件打字机
Absolute tanks of electric typewriters.
用起来一定很有趣
Rather fun to use.
再来看看这超级古旧的上世纪七八十年代显示技术
Aw man, the late '70s and early '80s display of technology that's goin' on here.
这台松下VCR录放机
This Panasonic VCR, my goodness.
这设计看上去很不错
What a fantastic looking design!
型号应该是PV-1210X？
I think the model number is PV-1210X?
不论如何，磁带槽确实好用
Either way, top loaders, top-notch.
好吧，看起来如此，但可能用起来没那么可靠
Well, visually. Maybe not so much in reliability.
Ohh，这蓝砖头是啥啊
Oh, we got something blue over here.
这是个嘛玩意
What is this?
这是台Fisher电热板，型号600T
We have a Fisher Thermix Hotplate Model 600T.
确实，它很能忍辱负重
Indeed. It looks very well-used.
谁知道呢，我只是因为它的蓝色才来看看
I don't know, I was just attracted to it because of the blue.
要是个又是个蓝的又要插在墙上供电的话，我兴许会喜欢
If it's blue and it plugs into a wall, I probably like it.
像这个，我是说，看到这个蓝色电器的话
Like this. I mean, speaking of blue electronics.
这是台Heathkit牌数字电路实验台
What we have here is a Heathkit Digital Design Experimenter.
这玩意可以干许多事情
And Heathkit made a lot of these type of things.
我自己有几台，但从没见过这个型号的
I have a couple myself, but I've never seen this one in particular.
基本上就这玩意可以把电路或者电动门之类的玩意的给搞乱
Basically just one of those devices to let you mess around with digital logic and electrical gates, and yeah,
只需一些电线和芯片之类的东西
you just need some wires and some chips and whatever.
你就可以大搞事情
You can make things happen on here.
在二手店看见挺酷的
Really cool to see in a thrift store.
从这走过来是一件我经常在Goodwill看见的大件
Across from here is another slightly different thing I normally see at Goodwill.
是台HPDesignjet 500宽式打印机与绘图仪
This is an HP Designjet 500 wide format printer/plotter.
卖2100元（300美元）
It's $300.
这看上去挺合适的
That seems, I don't know, somewhat reasonable.
绝对是个大件
An absolutely massive thing.
这玩意可以打印一米零六（42英寸）宽的纸张
It's like 42 inches that it can print across.
而且适配Windows 95
It can work on Windows 95 and such,
所以，这不得不令人敬仰
so, again, just absolutely massive.
正当我走出去的时候
And then as I was about to walk out,
我看见了这个角落里
I noticed on the end of the counter here
这大个TEAC箱子，准确地说，两个
this big old TEAC box, or a couple of 'em, really.
立体声磁带卡座，型号A-4010S
Stereo tape deck A-4010S.
1400元（200美元）出售
Was $200 and, oh,
而且里面是一台品相不错的
there is a rather lovely looking
开盘磁带录音机
reel-to-reel tape recorder in here.
唉，要是其附带长线缆
Aw man, if it had or took larger spools,
更大滚轮的话，我兴许会买走
larger reels, I suppose, then definitely would have gotten it.
我在这市场一直在找一类开盘磁带机
I am in the market for a specific type of reel-to-reel tape recorder,
但不是这台
but this wasn't quite the one.
但能看到亦是三生有幸，尤其是箱封的
Still really awesome to see, especially in the box.
这里还有一个
And then one more thing over across from there.
也不知为何没有放在电子区
I don't know why this wasn't back in the electronics,
但是上面的这个呢
but it was up here near the front.
是台德州仪器TI-99/4A电脑
We have a Texas Instruments TI-99/4A computer.
看看价格，1400块（200美元）？
Again, $200?
这家电把好多老电器标价很高
They're pricing a lot of these older things
比它们本来的价值还多
way higher than they should be.
举个例子，我不久前在Goodwill买了个全新未开封的仅需140元（20美元）
Like, I bought one of these basically brand new in box from Goodwill a while back and it was like 20 bucks.
我当然知道古董价格越老越贵
I know times are changin' and prices are goin' up,
但这个嘛......价格没标错吧
but come on, this is a little ridiculous.
1400块一台品相不佳的99/4A电脑？
200 bucks for a 99/4A that's a little bit beat up?
快给我去死吧！
Uh no, thank you.
来吧，为了做这集再去一家Goodwill
All right, on to the other Goodwill for this episode here.
是呀，这家我上个视频（在年初疫情没有爆发之时）曾说过
And yeah, this is the one if you remember, whatever the last video was,
它们正在这旁边盖了个门脸
they were building this building out beside it.
现在看上去呢
And it turns out
应该是家Panera面包店，是吧
it was supposed to be a Panera Bread, I believe?
他们在三月底完工
And they finished it up like right near the end of March,
正好遇到所有餐馆之类的门脸强制关门歇业
right about the time that all the restaurants and everything pretty much shut down.
所以对他们而言运气就很背:-(
So that was some rather poor timing on their part.
唉，现在开家餐馆真不是好时候:-(
What an awful era to try and open a new restaurant.
但走进Goodwill呢
But yeah, inside the Goodwill,
我立马被这个玻璃箱子里的东西给吸引了
I was immediately drawn to this on top of the glass case near the front.
这是个Corsair机箱，挺大一个
We got a Corsair computer case, a pretty beefy one.
他们要价525块钱（75美元）
They're charging 75 bucks for it,
对于这市场的老机箱的话，我觉得价格还行
which, I mean, a good deal to me if one was in the market for this type of big old case.
下头的这个呢
And down below that
是个盒装的通用电气的便携唱机
was a boxed portable phonograph from General Electric.
我没拿出来好好看看
I didn't take it out, couldn't get a good look at it,
但是这是有原包装的唱机啊，挺强的
but, still, record player in the box. It's kinda cool.
你要好奇的话，它长这样
This is what it actually looks like if you're curious.
不得不说，这橙色加米黄的配色十分耐人
I gotta say, I love anything with orange and beige as a combo.
从那边走过来的话
Across from there on one of their tables up near the front
我看见了这个复古设备，上面的颜色不错
we got another bit of retro stuff with some nice color going on.
一个Lady Schick Consolette电吹风
A Lady Schick Consolette hair dryer.
这个天蓝色太空时代（60年代）设计之类的
That baby blue Space Age design and everything, dude.
仅仅是个电吹风，但是我喜欢
Just a hairdryer thing, but I like it.
你懂的，我一直很喜欢这个
I also have always liked these, you know?
只是个地球仪，但它的设计呀......
It's just a globe, but it's the way it's put together.
反正这只是一个地球仪
And yeah, this is one that's just actually a globe.
好像记得有一类还能打开地球
They also have some that fold open,
然后把饮料放入
you could put drinks inside,
但这只有一个地球
but this is a globe.
只是一个地球
It's just a globe.
好吧
I approve.
我的妈呀，这玩意真损三观
Oh dear, what in the world is this?
玻璃里边罩着几个玩偶
Got a few dolls that had been stuck inside this glass case,
很明显她们晚上苏醒起来作乱
no doubt because they're haunted and come to life at night
然后要你精尽人亡:-(
and try to murder you or something.
嘿，这木纹
Oh hey, wood grain.
我们又看见了个大件
We got some things over here.
这玩意被人买走了
This item has been sold.
那是当然！
Well, of course it has!
那就看看吧
Just take a look at that.
这有一个迷你冰箱
That's a rather attractive mini fridge,
一看就很普通
you know, in the kind of really ugly way.
呵，这有个更小的
And hey, we have an even minier mini fridge,
或者只是个冷藏室
or maybe this is a freezer.
我觉得是个冰箱
I think it's a fridge.
毕竟三洋制造
This is a Sanyo, though.
这老牌子不错，而且呢
I dig that old logo and, yeah.
就算不是一个牌子，设计语言也相近
Very similar design, considering it's not the same brand.
再来看看这个折叠椅
Aw man, this folding chair.
给小朋友用的
This is a kid's folding chair,
但是孩子一定想要个正好的，但这个嘛
but as a kid, we used to have some chairs that were like exactly this but, you know,
正常人都觉得大了点
larger for normal-sized people.
这条带上的破损看上去很熟悉
There's something particular about the way that these bits on here just deteriorated.
童年回忆啊
It brings back such strange memories
诸如这条带按纹路裂开这类的
of, like, picking it apart.
确实，这玩意确实让我想起了一个个鲜活的回忆
The weirdest things bring back certain very vivid memories.
再来看看这个TV
Check out this TV over here.
或者是个显示器？
Is it a monitor? I don't know.
然而是戴尔制造
It's from Dell, though.
设计得倒也圆滑
It's actually a rather slick design.
是啊，我只是喜欢这个白色外壳
Yeah, I just like the white casing that it's in.
总觉得与那些灰的啊，银的啊，黑的啊很不一样
I don't know, it's kinda different from all those silver, gray, black monitors you normally see.
有人来点装派的碗吗？
Anybody need some pie tins?
这有很多，至少十个
There's a lot of them, at least 10 pie tins.
这些一收70（10美元）
It's $10 for a box of those.
还行吧......
Cool.
好吧，这玩意绝对是这的王者
Alrighty, now this is an absolute winner here.
看看这个由Gulbranson生产的Equinox 380-X Music Computer
Look at this. This is an Equinox 380-X Music Computer from Gulbransen.
是啊，我对这些电风琴相关的东西都很感兴趣
Yeah, I'm attracted to any of these kind of organ-type setups,
但这个就很特别
but this one in particular
这么多的设备把你包围了
with the surround design here just envelops you,
还有两个手感好的按钮，节拍选择器
and touch-sensitive buttons, and rhythm switches,
还插了个卡带加载点买来的附件
and it's got this cartridge loading thing where you can add expander pack carts
诸如新节奏之类的
to add new rhythms and sounds or something.
看，这设计确实赏心悦目
Dude, just an amazing looking design.
仅需700元（100美元）就能到手
It's $100.
真是巨大的的电子怪兽
Monstrously huge.
不知道这玩意用起来如何
Don't know how well it actually works or anything,
但是呢，这是Music Computer啊
but yeah, the Music Computer.
之前不知道，但现在知道了
Didn't know that existed, now I'm glad I know it does.
看，我们在这电子区看见了一个NMB键盘
Oh hey, we got an NMB keyboard over here in the electronics section.
可惜按键手感不好
Unfortunately, the switches suck.
但也没有那么糟
But still, not the worst keyboard.
它有上世纪九十年代的设计，所以还行
It's got that late '90s aesthetic, so that's cool.
看看这里的显示器
Check out this monitor over here.
这又是个嘛？
What is going on with this?
这是台Tandberg 1700
This is a Tandberg 1700.
这上面有个扬声器和十分大个的摄像头
It's got speakers and a big ol' camera on top,
再看看这一大堆插口
and yeah, look at all these connections.
原来这不只是个显示器
Turns out this is not just a monitor,
这是个全功能视频会议终端
this is like a full-on video conferencing terminal,
在办公室里称为行政管理中心
a so-called executive control center designed for offices.
对我而言，这是头一回见
I gotta say, that is a first for me.
之前在Goodwill从来没见过
Never seen one of these before at Goodwill.
可惜没附带适配器
Shame it didn't have the power supply.
也许再想一下我就买了
I might have picked it up just on a whim.
开开视野也挺好
It was also nice to see
这还有一个三星SyncMaster显示器
this Samsung SyncMaster monitor here,
仅仅是这个4:3显示比例
just 'cause of the four three aspect ratio
而且外壳也不是那种黑的灰的
and it's not yet another black gray monitor.
看着也很稀奇
Always nice to see.
我又看见一个Soundesign的东西
I got another Soundesign thing over here.
这倒像是我小时候看到的儿童CD播放器
This almost looks like one of those toy CD players I used to see as a kid,
但这个是个正经的CD播放器啊
but nah, this was an actual CD player.
只是这个设计十分奇怪
It's just got the most rounded weird design to it.
看上去像个玩具
It kinda looks like a toy.
只是......为啥要有儿童CD机呢？
Just... what in the world were they thinking?
不过呢，来看看这个飞机相关的
Oh hey, down here I see a flight thingy.
看见了一个飞行控制器
Got a yoke setup of some kind.
当然，给电脑用的
Yeah, for PCs.
底下是“高质量”的吸盘
Those "high-quality" suction cups on the bottom.
十五针的接口
15-pin game port connection, yeah.
好吧，并不需要，但看见也挺好玩的
Don't need any of these, but it's kinda cool to see.
我的天，看看这些在底下的老电器
Oh man, and check out the old down here.
这虽然品相不太好吧
This is kind of not in the best shape,
但是看看，看上去很厉害
but dude, it looks cool.
商标已经看不清了。Waurarioughoough?
I cannot read the brand. Waurarioughoough?
但这是种加法器啊，同志
But that's a heck of an adding machine, man.
再看这个鹤立鸡群的东西
Oh hey, this stood out from the crowd.
这可是JVC生产的的S-VHS高级S-Video线缆呢
We've got a S-VHS high grade S-VIDEO cable from JVC,
这可捡到好货了
which is perfect.
我实际上一直给我的JVC S-VHS VCR播放机找一个这个
I was actually just looking for one of these for my JVC S-VHS VCR.
所以这可不可错过
So, yeah, I'm gonna grab it.
为何不呢？这还没开封呢
Why not? It's still in the package.
看上去还没用呢
Doesn't look used at all.
然后这又是个嘛？
And what in the world is this?
NutriGuide Extreme Zone.
好吧，这就是种营养计算机
Oh okay, so it's a nutrition calculator
口袋电脑之类的吧
pocket computer-type of thing,
内置超过一万种食物成分
with over 10,000 foods in the database,
包括4500种外面餐贩和饭馆做的吃的
including 4,500 dining out and restaurant foods.
挺好奇是从哪些家饭馆搞来的数据
Kinda curious exactly what restaurants they included.
我的天啊！这是台老Easy-Bake Oven（简易烤箱）
Oh man, wow! This is an old Easy-Bake Oven right here.
看看这包装
Check out that packaging.
简易，安全，超过五百万家庭的选择
Simple, safe, fun, over five million ovens sold.
但这玩意简直了......
My goodness, though.
看那个烤箱
Look at that oven.
这有个外观概览
That is a design right there.
呵，这些电把啊！
Oh, what a delightful little assortment of flashlights.
他们一定花了心思把这些放在这里
Somebody put some time into stacking these up.
还有这堆机油滤清器
Also appreciate these old oil filters, you know.
它们在店里可不常见
They're not something you see very often,
尤其是这包装
especially in the packaging.
看这些老Sears手电，一个可充电的氪气灯
Look at this old Sears flashlight, a rechargeable Krypton.
是啊，氪气灯泡
Oh, it's got a Krypton bulb.
But yeah,还有底部的充电插头
plug right there in the bottom,
八十年代的充电手电，这就很好
rechargeable flashlight from the '80s, that is neat.
还有这真空吸尘器也挺好
Also neat, look at this vacuum.
在最丑的地方倒看得顺眼
Oh the design is beautiful, in that most hideous of ways.
Rainbow（彩虹）牌的，从来没听说过
It's a Rainbow vacuum, never heard of that.
但总体看来呢
But this entire design,
就是你早已忘记的老设计，然后现在你看见，你会想：“这怎么还有呢？”
that's the kind of hideous that you forget about and then here it is and you're like, how?
走过音像区呢，这里倒是有些
Over in the media, and there was actually a decent little assortment,
至少和平常不一样的，是这些八轨磁带
at least compared to what I normally see of 8-track tapes in here.
我并不特别需要
Nothing I'm necessarily looking for,
但是呢，八轨磁带万岁！
but, you know, yay 8-tracks!
下面呢就是些唱片
And then down below that in the records,
那个很引人注目
this stood out for obvious reasons.
《和AMECO公司电码课学习摩斯电码》
Learn Code with the AMECO Code Course.
发送教程，接收教程，通俗易懂
How to send, how to receive, easy to learn.
是的，这就是播放摩斯电码的唱片
Yeah, this is Morse code on vinyl.
你完全无法抗拒！
There's no way I'm not getting this!
还是双唱片
Two 12-inch records.
那更好了，你现在是我的了！
Absolutely, you are mine.
正当我要出去之时
And then one last thing as I was heading out
我碰巧看见这个小巧玲珑的索尼大法VAIO鼠标
I happened to notice this cute little Sony VAIO mouse
就在这些电缆电线上面
just hanging around on top of the cables and cords.
我并不需要，但我很喜欢
I don't need it, but I kinda like it.
只是一个小小的PS/2鼠标
It's just a little PS/2 mouse.
所以，为何不要呢？
Sure, why not?
以上是本集LGR淘二手淘来的好货
And that is it for the 45th episode of LGR Thrifts.
和以往有点不同，也没买多少
Bit of a different one, didn't pick up very much.
但是呢，这些东西都很酷啊！
But dang, there were some cool things out there to see.
而且你也知道，我对拥有这些东西感到高兴
And you know what, I'm happy with these couple of things here.
我搞来了这个奇怪的《学习摩斯电码》唱片
I got this weird Learn Code vinyl record,
还有这个高品质S-Video线缆
I got a nice high grade S-VIDEO cable,
还有这个小巧的索尼大法VAIO鼠标
and a little Sony VAIO mouse
正好扩充我关于VAIO的东西库存，何乐而不为呢？
for one of the Sony VAIOs I have, why not?
当然，你一定要听听这个摩斯电码唱片
But yeah, seriously, you know you gotta hear this Learn Code record.
它听起来是怎么样的呢？
What does this thing even sound like?
好吧，如你所愿
Well, it's exactly what you'd expect.
A B C D E
．━ /━．．．/━ ．━．/━ ．．/．
挺喜欢的
I love this.
LAUGHS=哈哈
.-.. .- ..- --. .... ...
目前而言，这简直是我拥有的最傻，最没劲的一张唱片了
This is the stupidest, the greatest, the best dumbest thing I have on vinyl, just about.
不管了，我自己有很多奇怪的唱片
I don't know, I have some pretty weird stuff on vinyl
但这是这其中比较好的了
but this is one of those records that is just perfect
而且这玩意存在真好
and I'm glad it exists.
无论如何，正片结束
Anyway, that is it for this episode.
我通常会收到一堆你们出去淘二手战利品的照片
And I usually have a whole lot of your submissions of things you found going thrifting here at the end,
但很明显你们现在没有以前出去那么勤快了
but obviously with people not really going out nearly as much,
最近收到的也少了，我也很能理解
there hasn't been as much submitted, which is fine, totally makes sense.
你懂的，在外要做好防护
You know, stay safe out there, obviously.
现在很凶险，你也看见了
Times are bizarre and it is what it is.
当然我呢，也将遵循我当地的防疫要求
As for me, I'm gonna continue following my own local guidelines
尽量保持安全
and just trying to be as safe as possible.
我也不知下一集啥时可以做出来
Don't really know when the next episode is gonna be at this point, seriously.
所以我希望你看得愉快
So I hope that you enjoyed this one,
我们下集淘二手见，甭管啥时能搞出来了
and we'll see you in the next Thrifts, whenever that may be.
最终会有的
One of these days.
一如既往，感谢收看，外出注意安全
As always, thanks for watching and stay safe out there.
本视频由SuperBart翻译，原作者LGR